Finding Aid for Michigan Memorial Phoenix Project Records, 1947-2003
Bentley Historical Library
- Research, 1948-2003
  - Research Grants, Nos. 1-816, 1948-1996
    - #1-#200
      - Analysis of Pharmaceuticals by Neutron Activation, W.W. Meinke, [151.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Virus as an Indicator of Irradiation Induced Alterations in Cancer Cells, R.T. Christian, P.P. Ludovici, [152.] (Box 40)
      - Cytological and histochemical changes in the parenchyma of lymph glands of the rat resulting from x-irradiation, E.C. Pliske, [153.] (Box 40)
      - Development of a Device for Photographing the Tracks of High Energy Particles, L.W. Jones and M.L. Perl, [154.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Genetic effects of low-dosage radiation, R.D. Milkman, [155.] (Box 40)
      - Thyroid cancer, enzymology and immunology, W.H. Beierwaltes, [156.] (Box 40)
      - Rehabilitation of Chrysler Gift Equipment for Liquid Metal..., F.G. Hammitt, [157.] (Box 40)
      - Tissue Culture Studies in Cellular Metabolism, H.C. Jordan, [158.] (Box 40)
      - Effect of High Concentration of Iron on Rate of Heme Synthesis, R.C. Bishop, [159.] (Box 40)
      - Study of Flavor Problem in Irradiated Foods, L.E. Brownell, [160.] (Box 40)
      - Experimental Study of K+ Meson Scattering, D.I. Meyer and K.M. Terwilliger, [161.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Location & Quantitation of Gastrointestinal Bleeding, J.C. Floyd, [162.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Biosynthesis of Eydroxyproline II. The Chemical Synthesis of Peptides Containing C14-labeled L-prolime, M. Levine, [163.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Investigation of Effect of Ionizing Radiation Upon Amount of Certain Enymes Contained in Lymphoid Tissue, R.L. Hunter, [164.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Control of Melanization in Candida, A.S. Sussman, [165.] (Box 40)
      - The Implications of Evasion in the Negotiation of Nuclear Disarmament, J.D. Singer, [166.]; 2 folders (Box 40)
      - Investigation of Chemical Effect of Nuclear Transformations in Halogen-Alkyl Halide Systems, A.A. Gordus, [167.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Low Prandtl Number Natural Convection Study, F.G. Hammitt, [168.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Glyconeogenesis & Enzymes of the Glyoxylate Cycle, J.F. Hogg, [169.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Metabolism of D-glucaric Acid by Escherichia coli, H.J. Blumenthal, [170.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Thermodynamic Properties of Uranium Monocarbide, M.J. Sinnott, [171.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Studies on the Mechanism of Action of Condensing Enzyme, P.A. Srere, [172.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - The Uptake & Translocation of Water & Nutrients by Clones of Populus Species as Measured by Radioactive Tracers, R. Zahner, [173.]; 2 folders
      - Legal problems in radiation injury situations, S.D. Estep, [174.] (Box 41)
      - I 131 Diodrast Renal Clearance, W.H. Beierwaltes, [175.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - The Penetration of Various Form of Algae into Rapid Sand Filters, J.A. Borchardt, [176.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Study on the Biological Cycle of Megakaryocytes & Platelets, G. Raccuglia, [177.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Gas Chromatographic Separation and Compounds, A.A. Gordus, [178.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Mechanics of the Growth & Interaction of Vapor Bubbles, J.A. Clark, [179.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Activity of Rabbit Anti-tumor Globulin Following Enzymatic Digestion, F. Whitehouse, [180.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Effects of Low Level & Chronic Radiation on Growth of Animal Cells in vitro, D.J. Merchant, [181.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - The Origin of Androgenic Steroids in the Human Ovary, G.S. Duboff, [182.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Secondary Amplification of the Fluoroscopic Image by Optical Image Intensifier, W.M. Whitehouse, [183.] (Box 41)
      - An investigation of the effect of gamma radiation upon enzyme changes..., R.L. Hunter, [184.] (Box 41)
      - Study of the Human Circulation Using Radioactive Krypton..., W.S. Wilson, [185.] (Box 41)
      - Endocrine Influences on Amino Acid Transport in Man, H.N. Christensen, [186.] (Box 41)
      - Hematology Research, M.C. Meyers, [187.] (Box 41)
      - The Metabolism of -- Hydroxyglutamic Acid in Plants, E.E. Dekker, [188.] (Box 41)
      - Rates of Fibrinogen Turnover, J.A. Penner, [189.] (Box 41)
      - Studies on the Effect of Thyrotropin on the Concentration and Turnover of Nucleic Acids, J.Matovinovic, [190.] (Box 41)
      - Activation Analysis Using a Neutron Generator, W.W. Meinke, [191.] (Box 41)
      - Uptake, transport, and effects of radioactive materials in aquatic ecosystems, D.C. Chandler, [192.] (Box 41)
      - Thermodynamic Properties of Liquid Uranium Alloys, R.D. Pehlke, [193.] (Box 41)
      - Isolation and Identification of Lipids Labeled with Radioactive Isotopes, B.W. Agranoff, [194.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Study of the Etiology of Cleft Palate Formation, J.K. Avery, [195.] (Box 41)
      - Neutron Damage Studies on Mammalian Tissue Cells, G.H. Whipple, [196.] (Box 41)
      - Investigation of Properties of Impurities in Aluminum Oxide, C. Kikuchi, [197.] (Box 41)
      - Calcium 48 Enrichment of Natural Calcium, A.A. Gordus, [198.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
      - Parenteral Food Uptake by Freshwater Fishes, J.E. Bardach, [199.] (Box 41)
      - Renoscanning, T. Haynie, [200.]; 2 folders (Box 41)
    - #201-#400
      - .Factors Influencing Membrane Permeability of Gastric Cells, D.R. Kahn, [201.] (Box 41)
      - Thermonuclear Fusion Laboratory, E. Martin, [202.] (Box 41)
      - Radioactive dating of rocks from Huerfano Parking, Colorado, L.I. Briggs, [203.] (Box 41)
      - Mineralogy of Rare Earth Thorium Deposits, E.W. Heinrich, [204.] (Box 41)
      - Investigation of the Effects of Ship's Motion on Boiling Water Reactors, G.L. West, [205.] (Box 41)
      - Tracer studies on protein synthesis in differentiating cells, N.E. Kemp, [206.] (Box 41)
      - Self-Irradiation Damage in a Labeled Macromolecule, P.C. Rajam, [207.] (Box 41)
      - Carcinogenesis by Reactor Produced Radiation, C.J. Shellabarger, [208.] (Box 41)
      - Clinical Evaluation of Radioactive Tracer Techniques as Applied to Neoplasms of the Female Genital Tract, G.W. Morley, [209.] (Box 41)
      - I-131 Labeled Fat in Myocardial Infarct Patients, J.C. Sisson, [210.] (Box 41)
      - Atomic Energy Policy in France, R. Pierce, [211.] (Box 41)
      - Summer Conference on Neutron Physics, P. Zweifel, [212.] (Box 41)
      - Hydrocarbon Reactions Promoted by Ionizing Radiation, M. Martin, [213.] (Box 41)
      - Thermoelectric Coefficient Measuring Instrument, C. Kikuchi, [214.] (Box 41)
      - Development of Solid State Fast Neutron Spectrometer, J.S. King, [215.] (Box 41)
      - Cartilage Formation in Somites of Normal & T/T Mice, J.N. Cather, [216.] (Box 41)
      - Biosynthetic Function of Cytoplasmic Granules in Protozoa, J.F. Hogg, [217.] (Box 41)
      - Autoradiographic Tracing in Antigenically Stimulated Cells in the Germinal center of the Rabbit Spleen, A.G. Johnson, [218.] (Box 41)
      - Biosynthesis of Phenazine-1-Carboxylic Acid, M.E. Levitch, [219.] (Box 41)
      - Study of Short Term Alterations in Tissue Distribution of Radioactive Cesium, Ribidium and Mercury, E.A. Carr, [220.] (Box 41)
      - Tritiated Thyrotropin, T.P. Haynie, [221.] (Box 41)
      - Study of the Effect of Thiouracil on the Metabolism of Nuclear Acids in the Thyroid Gland of the Guinea Pig, J. Matovinovic, [222.] (Box 41)
      - High Flux Heat Transfer Through Alkalai Metal Vapors, R.E. Balzhiser, [223.] (Box 41)
      - Dating of Relics by C14 Analysis, H.R. Crane, [224.] (Box 42)
      - Spectra of Isotopic Molecules, A.A. Gordus, [225.] (Box 42)
      - Activation Analysis Using Isotopes with Very Short Half Lives, W.W. Meinke, [226.] (Box 42)
      - Studies on Surface Heterogeneity by Radioisotopic Methods, G. Parravano, [227.] (Box 42)
      - Distribution of Radioisotopes in Brain, B.W. Agranoff, [228.] (Box 42)
      - K42 Movements in Isolated Frog Iris, L. Barr, [229.] (Box 42)
      - Interrelationship Between Plasma Volume and Cardiac Output, J. Conway, [230.] (Box 42)
      - Study of Bone Marrow Kinetics, G. Raccuglia, [231.] (Box 42)
      - Total Blood Volumes in Surgical Patients, G. Steude, [232.] (Box 42)
      - Cryomagnetic Studies of Lanthanide and Actinide Chalcogenides, E.F. Westrum, [233.] (Box 42)
      - Comparative Study of Radiation Safety, G. H. Whipple, [234.] (Box 42)
      - Plasma Equations, R.K. Osborn, [235.] (Box 42)
      - Stability of Oscillations in a Hot Plasma, R.S.B. Ong, [236.] (Box 42)
      - Investigations on the Incorporation of H3-Thymidine by Internodes of Avena, P.B. Kaufman, [237.] (Box 42)
      - Biosynthesis of the Blood Group Substances, D. Aminoff, [238.] (Box 42)
      - Prognostic Value of CX-Reactive Protein in X-Irradiated Rabbits, B.S. Berlin, [239.] (Box 42)
      - The Biosynthesis of Epidermal Keratin, M.E. Levitch, [240.] (Box 42)
      - Pancreas Scanning with Selenium 75, Selenomethionine, George D. Zuikuma, [241.] (Box 42)
      - Lung Scanning, H.J. Dworkin, [242.] (Box 42)
      - The Effects of 'Soft' Radiation on Development of Some Wood Boring Insects, F.B. Knight, [243.] (Box 42)
      - Line Identifications in the Spectra of Peculiar Stars, W.P. Bidelman, [244.] (Box 42)
      - Dynamic Modeling of Rain-Producing Systems, A.N. Dingle, [245.] (Box 42)
      - Fast Event Timing Using Gamma Ray Beams, G.L. Gyorey, [246.] (Box 42)
      - Potassium-Argon Age Determination of Precambrian Rocks in the Arkansas River Canyon Area-Colorado, E.W. Heinrich, [247.] (Box 42)
      - Interaction Between a Moving Body and a Highly Rarefied Plasma,V.C. Liu, [248.] (Box 42)
      - Chemistry of Technetium, C.L. Rulfs, [249.] (Box 42)
      - Approximate Approaches to Transport Theory, F.C. Shure, [250.] (Box 42)
      - Vertical and Lateral Movement of Soil-Inhabiting Cicada Nymphs, T.E. Moore, [251.] (Box 42)
      - A Study of the Action of Cobalt on Lipid Metabolism, W.D. Block, [252.] (Box 42)
      - Controlled Variation of X-Ray Lethal Dose in Planarians, J.V. McDonnell, [253.] (Box 42)
      - The Policy Dimensions of Congressional Action on Peacetime Uses of Atomic Energy, W.E. Miller, [254.] (Box 42)
      - Cortisone and Cleft Palate in A/Jax Mice, J.K. Avery, [255.] (Box 42)
      - Study of the Concentration of Cesium 131 and 134 in Normal, Ischemic and Infarcted Myocardium, Edward A. Carr, Jr., [256.] (Box 42)
      - Incorporation of 3H Thymidine Into Herpes Simplex Infected-Human Amnion Cells, R.T. Christian, [257.] (Box 42)
      - Skeletal Muscle Metabolism and Thyroid Hormone, J.C. Sisson, [258.] (Box 42)
      - Summer Symposium in Radiation Biology, C.J. Shellabarger, [259.] (Box 42)
      - Isotopic Spectra and High-Energy Photochemical Reactions, A.A. Gordus, [260.] (Box 42)
      - High-Energy Interactions Simulated Using an Analog Computer, A.A. Gordus, [261.] (Box 42)
      - Universal Instabilities in Thermonuclear Plasma, T. Kammash, [262.] (Box 42)
      - Stability of a Hot, Long-lived Plasma, R.S.B. Ong, [263.] (Box 42)
      - Transient Heat Transfer in Laminar Flow of Bingham Plastics through Circular Tubes w/ Internal Heat-Gen., Wen-Tei Yang, [264.] (Box 42)
      - Tritium Labeled Purines and Pyrimidines into Influenze Virus Infected Tissue Culture Cells, H.F. Maassab, [265.] (Box 42)
      - Autoradiography of the Larval Fat Cell of Drosophila, T.M. Rizki, [266.] (Box 42)
      - An Analysis of the Role of Bacteria as a Source of Food for Zooplankton by Use of Carbon-14 Starch, G.W. Saunders, [267.] (Box 42)
      - The Test Ban Negotiations, H.K. Jacobson, [268.] (Box 42)
      - Study of Erythropoiesis Regulation, P.H. Abbrecht, [269.] (Box 42)
      - Lipogenetic Factors in Human Serum Proteins, L. Power, [270.] (Box 42)
      - Transient Solidification Studies in Metals, P.K. Trojan, [271.] (Box 42)
      - Diffusion of Radioactive Stack Gases Near Large Buildings, G.H. Whipple, [272.] (Box 42)
      - Laramide (Tertiary) Orogenic History of the Southern Rocky Mountains, Colorado, L.I. Briggs, [273.] (Box 42)
      - NaF:UO2++ and LiF:UO2++ as Neutron Detectors, C. Kikuchi, [274.] (Box 42)
      - Low Temperature Scintillation Measurements, G.F. Knoll, [275.] (Box 42)
      - Application of Coulometric Techniques to Neutron Activation Analysis & Nuclear Spectroscopy, H.B. Mark, [276.] (Box 42)
      - Use of Counting Techniques to Determine the Purity of Superpure Materials, J.E. Powers, [277.] (Box 42)
      - The Chemistry of Technetium, C.L. Rulfs, [278.] (Box 42)
      - Thermal Neutron Scattering from High Polymers, G.C. Summerfield, [279.] (Box 42)
      - Magnetic Susceptibilities of Nuclear Materials, E.F. Westrum, [280.] (Box 42)
      - Natural Convective Heat & Mass Transfer in Bingham Plastics in Closed, Vertical Cyl. Vessels w/Int. Heat Sources, W.J. Yang, [281.] (Box 42)
      - Mitochondrial Biosynthesis of Lipids, K.S. Henley, [282.] (Box 42)
      - Preliminary Study of Effects of Con. Low-Level Radiation on a Virus-Host Cell System, D.J. Merchant, [283.] (Box 42)
      - Enrich. of Proteins w/Amino Acid Res. Employing C14-Amino Acids & a Bifunc. Reagent; Chem. & Immunochemical Studies, J.S. Ram, [284.] (Box 42)
      - Albumin Profile in Kidney Medulla, W.S. Wilde, [285.] (Box 42)
      - Neutron Activation Analysis of Arch. Materials, J.B. Griffin, [286.] (Box 42)
      - Diabetic Diarrhea, R.J. Bolt, [287.] (Box 42)
      - The Use of Low Molecular Weight Dextran in Standard Second & Third Degree Burns, R.O. Dingman, [288.] (Box 42)
      - The Metabolism of Radiofluorine in Dog & Humans, & Its Application in the Study of Bone Tumors & Fractile Healing, N.F. Moon, [289.] (Box 42)
      - Thermonuclear Research, W. Kerr, [290.] (Box 42)
      - Research Leader in Zoology, D.E.S. Brown, [291.] (Box 42)
      - Study of X-Rays Emitted from Fragments in Thermal Neutron Fission, H. Griffin, [292.] (Box 42)
      - Direct Energy Conv. Concepts Using Liquid Metal MHD Systems, F.G. Hammitt, [293.] (Box 42)
      - Variable Temperature (10°K to 100°K) Cryostat for Neutron Scattering, J.S. King, [294.] (Box 42)
      - Mössbauer Spectra of Certain Iron and Tin Compounds, P.G. Rasmussen, [295.] (Box 42)
      - Application of Radioactivation Analyses to Wood, E.L. Ellis, [296.] (Box 42)
      - In Vivo Perfusion of the Human Ovary, R.B. Jaffe, [297.] (Box 42)
      - Tracer Studies on Somatic Radiation Damage in Aquatic Vertebrates, N.E. Kemp, [298.] (Box 42)
      - Metabolism and Physiological Role of Conjugated Steroids, M. Mason, [299.] (Box 42)
      - Ontogenesis of Permeability of the Blood-Brain Barrier to Na-22 in the Rat, J.B. Ranck, [300.] (Box 42)
      - Psychological Commitment to Roles of a Defense-Oriented Social System, M. Pilisuk, [301.] (Box 42)
      - Kinetics of Peritoneal Transfer of Sodium Bisulfite, J.A. Greene, [302.] (Box 42)
      - Radiometry by Thermoluminescence, M.T.J. Hilger, [303.] (Box 42)
      - C14-Aminocyclopentane Carboxylic Acid as an Agent for Pancreatic Visualization, S.M. Lindenauer, [304.] (Box 43)
      - Low PBI Values & Apparent Hypothyroidism after I131 Therapy for Thryotoxicosis, J. Matovinovic, [305.] (Box 43)
      - Radioiodination: Its Effect Upon the Hormonal and Immunological Activity of Human Chorionic Gonadotropin, A.R. Midgley, [306.] (Box 43)
      - A Mathematical Study of Particle Movement in Fluidized Systems, J.D. Murray, [307.] (Box 43)
      - Infra-Red and Neutron Scattering Spectra from Deuterated Polyethylene, J.S. King and S. Krimm, [308.] (Box 43)
      - Selective Separation Techniques for the Determination of Metal Ions in Biological Systems Employing Neutron Activation Analysis, H.B. Mark, [309.] (Box 43)
      - Mossbauer Effect Studies of Lattice Defects, D.H. Vincent, [310.] (Box 43)
      - Growth Hormone Response to the Administration of Aminoacids, R.F. Knopf, [311.] (Box 43)
      - A Study of Potential Heterotrophy in Phytoplankton Under Near Natural Conditions by Use of C-14, G.W. Saunders, [312.] (Box 43)
      - Trace Metal Control of Biological Membrane Permeability, J.S. Schultz, [313.] (Box 43)
      - Studies on the Reaction Mechanism of Glutathione Reductase, C. Williams, [314.] (Box 43)
      - The International Control of Nuclear Weapons: A Comparative Analysis of Policy Preferences, D. Singer, [315.] (Box 43)
      - Localization of Radioactive Compounds, H.J. Cohn and J.C. Sisson, [316.] (Box 43)
      - The Synthesis of 5,6-Dihydroxyindole-2-C14 and I131 Iodinated Analogs for Distribution and Excretion Studies in Mice with Transplanted Melanomas, R.B. Counsell, [317.] (Box 43)
      - Measurement of the Spatial Dependence of the Cross Power Spectral Density of the Ford Nuc. Reactor, D.R. Bach, [318.] (Box 43)
      - Ultrasonic Wetter Wall Column, S. Fogler, [319.] (Box 43)
      - Neutron Activation Analysis of Alloys and Ceramics, A.A. Gordus, [320.] (Box 43)
      - Gamma-Ray Spectroscopy of Reactor Produced Nuclides, H.C. Griffin, [321.] (Box 43)
      - Analogies Between Impact and Cavitation Pitting, F.G. Hammitt, [322.] (Box 43)
      - Burnout in Natural Circulation Under Oscillating Flow conditions, J.B. Woodward, [323.] (Box 43)
      - Biosynthesis of Mammalian Glycoproteins, G. Bole and G. Jourdian, [324.] (Box 43)
      - A Model Study of the Role of Vit. B12 in Methionine-Methyl Synthesis, H. Elford, [325.] (Box 43)
      - The Mechanism of Action of Maleic Hydrazide on Plant Growth, L.D. Nooden, [326.] (Box 43)
      - Formate Metabolism, T.R. Tephly, [327.] (Box 43)
      - An Analysis of Nuclear Weapons Policy Preferences of State and Defense Department Officials, D. Singer and B. Mennis, [328.] (Box 43)
      - A Study of the Uptake and Distribution of Fluorine 18 in Bone and Bony Lesions, D. Woodbury, [329.] (Box 43)
      - Platelet and White Cell Incorporation of Selenomethionine, J.A. Penner, [330.] (Box 43)
      - A Study of Selected Properties of Neutron-Irradiated Type I & II Diamonds, R.M. Denning, [331.] (Box 43)
      - Minimum Time Control of Temp. Patterns in Nuclear Reactors, W.J. Yang, [332.] (Box 43)
      - Effects of Radiation on Select. of Variants in vitro Animal Cell Cultures, D.J. Merchant, [333.] (Box 43)
      - Studies on the Incorp. of Radioactive Nucleic Acid Precursors into Goldfish Brain, O.Z. Sellinger, [334.] (Box 43)
      - NATO and Nuclear Weap. A Dilemma for the United States, C. Inis, [335.] (Box 43)
      - Neutron Activ. Analysis of pigments of works of Art, A.A. Gordus and M. Johnson, [336.] (Box 43)
      - New Method for the Radioimmunological Assay of Insulin Employing Ethanol Precipitation etc., J.C. Floyd, [337.] (Box 43)
      - Development of a Double Isotope Dilution Derivative Method for the Determination of the Daily Rate, D. Rovner, [338.] (Box 43)
      - The Synthesis of F-labeled Organic Compounds, R.E. Counsell, [339.] (Box 43)
      - Somatic Radiation Damage During Metamorphosos or Regeneration in Aquatic Vertebrates, N. Kemp, [340.] (Box 43)
      - The Use of Radioactivity to Study Natural Convection, W.R. Debler, [341.] (Box 43)
      - Measurement of Dynamic Reactor Parameters Using Gamma Radiation, J.M. Carpenter, [342.] (Box 43)
      - The Use of Neutron Activation in Field Experiments Designed to Evaluate Silver Iodide as a Cloud Modification Agent, A.N. Dingle, [343.] (Box 43)
      - Two-Phase Flow Materials Attrition Control in Fluid Systems, F.G. Hammitt, [344.] (Box 43)
      - Magnesium Pemoline and Radio-sensitivity, B.S. Berlin and K.W. Cochran, [345.] (Box 43)
      - Mechanisms of Suppression of Antibody Formation by Ionizing Radiation, R.J. Porter, [346.] (Box 43)
      - Neutron Activation Analysis of Ancient and Medieval Coins, T.V. Buttrey, A.S. Ehrenkreutz, and A.A. Gordus, [347.] (Box 43)
      - Radiographic Examination of Egyptian Mummies, J.E. Harris, [348.] (Box 43)
      - Development of a Method for the Determination of Individual Estrogens Using Labeled Steroid Conjugates, U.T. Goebelsmann, [349.] (Box 43)
      - Gastric Pressure, Motility and Emptying: A Physiological Correlation, H.M. Pollard, [350.] (Box 43)
      - Completion of 50 Inch Cyclotron, M.L. Wiedenbeck, [351.] (Box 43)
      - Investigation of the Condensation of Cesium and Rubidium, R.E. Balzhiser, [352.] (Box 43)
      - Study of Plasma Ion Heating by Electron Beam-Plasma Interaction, W.D. Getty, [353.] (Box 43)
      - Nonlinear Theory of Electron Beam-Plasma Heating, J.E. Rowe, [354.] (Box 43)
      - Measurement of Thermal Neutron Absorption Cross-Sections with Emphasis on the Odd-Odd Nuclides, C. Kikuchi, [355.] (Box 43)
      - Differential Neutron Filter, J.S. King, [356.] (Box 43)
      - Gamma Ray Camera Design, G.F. Knoll, [357.] (Box 43)
      - Neutron Activation Analysis for Iodine, Bromine, & Chlorine in Waters from the L. Michigan and L. Superior Environment, J.W. Winchester, [358.] (Box 43)
      - Response of the Mongolian Gerbil (Meriones unguiculatus) to Acute Whole-Body Co-60 Irradiation, A.P. Jacobson, [359.] (Box 43)
      - An Electron Auto-radiographic Study of the Biosynthesis of Basement Membrane by Epithelial Cells, G.B. Pierce, [360.] (Box 43)
      - Assay of Erthrocyte Stimulating Factor, R.E. Easterling, [361.] (Box 43)
      - A Study of the Atmospheres of G-Dwarf Stars, J.A. Williams, [362.] (Box 43)
      - Radiation Effects on the Morphology of Cold-drawn Polyethylene, G.S.Y. Yeh, [363.] (Box 43)
      - New Measures of Nuclear Shape, J.C. Zorn, [364.] (Box 43)
      - New Method for Simultaneous Radioimmunoassay of Insulin and Growth Hormone, J.C. Floyd and R.F. Knopf, [365.] (Box 43)
      - Kidney Function in Estriol Excretion, U.T. Goebelsmann, [366.] (Box 43)
      - Effect of Extracorporeal Circulation upon Total Exchange of Potassium and Digitalis in Patients Undergoing Open Heart Operations, D.R. Kahn, [367.] (Box 44)
      - Development of a Radioimmunassay for Blood Renin, Lucas, Charles, [368.] (Box 44)
      - Biosynthetic Labeling of Rat Luteinizing Hormone, A.R. Midgley, [369.] (Box 44)
      - The Role of Carbon Dioxide in the Germination stimulation of Polyporus dryophilus var. vulpinus basidiospores, H.L. Morton, [370.] (Box 44)
      - Ultrastructural study of brown adipose tissue of the golden hamster, E.B. Smith, [371.] (Box 44)
      - Ionizing Radiation as a Negative Reinforcer in Rats, J.V. McConnell, [372.] (Box 44)
      - Genetic Homology and Host-Virus Association, E.B. Carew, [373.] (Box 44)
      - Neutron Activation -- A Method for the Detection and Characterization of Submicrogram Quantities of Nucleotide Oligosaccharides, G.W. Jourdian, [374.] (Box 44)
      - Synthesis of an Optimal Control of a Distributed Parameter Reactor, A.Z. Akcasu, [375.] (Box 44)
      - Investigation of Liquid Metal Condensation, R.E. Barry, [376.] (Box 44)
      - Peaceful Uses of Magnetic Resonance in Short-Lived Radioactive Nuclear States, R. Lewis and W. Williams, [377.] (Box 44)
      - Sulfur-Containing Polymeric Antiradiation Agents, C. Overberger, [378.] (Box 44)
      - Interaction of Ions with Super-fluid Helium, B. Springett, [379.] (Box 44)
      - Mossbauer Effect Studies of Lattice Defects, D.H. Vincent, [380.] (Box 44)
      - The Effects of X-Irradiation on Muscle Regeneration, B. Carlson, [381.] (Box 44)
      - Development of Improved Methods for Radioassay of 51CR in Stool As A Method for Determining Fecal Blood Loss, D. Fall and D. Kuiper, [382.] (Box 44)
      - Cell Division After Brain Injury in the Neonate, R. Isaacson, [383.] (Box 44)
      - Serum Steroid-Gonadotropin Interactions, R.B. Jaffe, [384.] (Box 44)
      - Characterization of Active Sites in Nuclear Phosphoproteins, L. Kleinsmith, [385.] (Box 44)
      - C-14 Fixation in Algal Cells and Cell Constituents Absolute Counting with Liquid Scintillation, D. Woodring, [386.] (Box 44)